Guide to the Nancy Blood papers, 1967-1977 RL.00121
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Nancy Blood papers
1967-1977
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Blood, Nancy
RL.00121
1.5 Linear Feet
Nancy Blood is a retired Durham County Public Libraries librarian and is also a feminist and LGBT rights activist. Accession (2009-0101) (1.5 lin. ft.; dated 1967-1977 and undated) consists of a subject file of printed materials discussing women's health, employment, art, feminism, academics, law, motherhood, etc. Acquired as part of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
750 items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
Gift, 2006 (2009-0101), 1.5 lin. ft.
Biographical / Historical Note
Nancy Blood is a retired Durham County Public Libraries librarian and is also a feminist and LGBT rights activist.
Collection Overview
Accession (2009-0101) (1.5 lin. ft.; dated 1967-1977 and undated) consists of a subject file of printed materials discussing women's health, employment, art, feminism, academics, law, motherhood, etc. Acquired as part of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
Feminism; Women -- Health and hygiene; Birth control; Child care; Women's rights -- United States; Women artists; United States; Blood, Nancy; Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture; Blood, Nancy; United Feminist Front
- Subject Files, 1 box
  Scope and Contents note
  Accession (2009-0101) (1.5 lin. ft.; dated 1967-1977 and undated) consists of a subject file of printed materials discussing women's health, employment, art, feminism, academics, law, motherhood, etc.
  - Arts, 1972-1973 and undated (Box 1)
  - Assault line, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Birth control, 1969-1976 (Box 1)
  - Bodies, 1967-1976 (Box 1)
  - Childcare, 1970-1975 (Box 1)
  - Drama and media, 1972-1976 (Box 1)
  - ERA, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Health, 1969-1975 (Box 1)
  - International women, 1972-1974 (Box 1)
  - Law and women, 1973-1977 (Box 1)
  - Man on woman, 1969-1974 (Box 1)
  - Monographic anthologies, 1970 and undated (Box 1)
  - Psychology and women, 1967-1973 (Box 1)
  - Public eye, 1969-1971 (Box 1)
  - Redstockings, Gloria Steinum, Flo Kennedy, 1975 and undated (Box 1)
  - Tracts, 1969-1971 (Box 1)
  - Tracts, 1972-1973 (Box 1)
  - Tracts, 1971 and undated (Box 1)
  - United Feminist Front (UFF), 1975 (Box 1)
  - Women in academia, 1971-1974 (Box 1)
  - Women and socialism, 1971-1974 (Box 1)
  - Women's centers, 1973 and undated (Box 1)
  - Work, 1975 and undated (Box 1)